[Music]
the pandemic has posed some serious
challenges in the pharmaceutical sector
and to help them navigate through these
turbulent times we bring you india risk
practitioners a special segment as a
part of india risk management awards the
corona virus pandemic is a complex
multifaceted crisis has resulted in
giving rise to various risks and
highlighted the importance of risk
management in india
very very critical to to keep all the
stakeholders involved right i think
the entire transformation will break
until unless you have the
you know the
the supply chain organized the consumer
organized right
into the part of the supply chain so for
example even today when we say pack and
trace our partner warehouses and our
partner retailers have bar coding that
shows where the product has
been manufactured generated supply each
and etcetera but we have no visibility
of the manufacturers
right that's a big challenge and the
same challenge the manufacturers will
face if they go downstream i think if
manufacturers can work with new age
companies like ours when we have pin
code level visibility
i think would be great for them to do
that i think the biggest thing that they
need is just an open mind um
you know
the ability to collaborate and move
quickly a few models will fail a few
attempts will not fructify but i think
at the end if we are able to make
something work
for the entire ecosystem i think nothing
like it well to nominate your
organization for the india risk
management awards visit the below link